[{"answer": "Sort what out?  Are my pages done", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They took 'em?  Who took 'em? my friend, what's going on..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I wasn't alone.  Wasn't my friend directing the picture you're in", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, whatever my friend's got, it's catching", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Too bad.  He says I'm a communist", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You know I'm not a communist, don't you, my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You ever been in this town before, to your knowledge", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "But what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The Bijou", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We live in a theater", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "They couldn't wait to see you", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "This is the staff of the Bijou", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who... are they", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh.  What... what time is it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Uh, thanks.  Good to see you again, too, uh..", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "... my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Have you always wanted to be a lawyer", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What did... what did I want to be", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So I guess this fellow belongs to you.  What's his name", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Cat.  That's simple.  I like it.  Hi, Cat", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "A loan to a man who ran his business into the ground and his son who can't account for the last nin", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Have you got a cigarette", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Motion to encourage the citizenry of my friend to help out the Bijou in any way they can..", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " ... short of allocation of city funds", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's all right, my friend", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes, my friend.  He's dead", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm here", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Did I what", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Would that be Miss my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "My girlfriend.  If she still is..", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " No.  No, not Miss my friend.  I'm talking about my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I wish you were coming with me", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Maybe we could train Cat to run the projector.  You know, a system of scratching posts, and gears, and levers..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I do", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend.  Hollywood, that place", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Sir, that is true", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "my friend?  We never met.  But I'd like to think I know him", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yet you're contradicting yourself. You earlier testified that you attended a meeting of a communist part", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Well, then, as what did you go", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Majestic_-The-(The-Bijou).txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend, I didn't give them the names. I wouldn't do that", "qsentId": 42}]